[
    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT included in Generic Process Models?",
        "a" : "Waterfall model",
        "b" : "Evolutionary development",
        "c" : "Formal systems development",
        "d" : "Use-based development",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 3
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT included in Specific Process Models?",
        "a" : "Incremental model",
        "b" : "Object-Based Development Model",
        "c" : "Spiral Development Model",
        "d" : "Package-Based Development Model",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 2
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT included in Characteristics of Software?",
        "a" : "Software does “wear out”",
        "b" : "Software is abstract and intangible",
        "c" : "Software is developed or engineered; it is not manufactured in the classical sense",
        "d" : "Most software is custom-built, rather than being assembled from existing components",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 1
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT included in Fundamental Process Activities of Software Process?",
        "a" : "Specification",
        "b" : "Development",
        "c" : "Validation",
        "d" : "Evolution",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 5
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of the Waterfall Model?",
        "a" : "Very clear from a managerial viewpoint - easy to model, plan, monitor, and understand",
        "b" : "Many existing tools support this model",
        "c" : "Development is relatively slow and deliberate and thus, results in solid, well-constructed systems",
        "d" : "Last explicit process model",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 4
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT a description of Waterfall model?",
        "a" : "Linear sequential model",
        "b" : "Describe a set of clear stages in the development process",
        "c" : "Based on engineering practice",
        "d" : "Still used for large systems engineering projects",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 5
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT a disadvantage of Evolutionary Development?",
        "a" : "Cost, time, and resource estimation is difficult",
        "b" : "Process is not visible",
        "c" : "Progress is difficult to measure",
        "d" : "Less effective than waterfall model",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 4
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT a description of Incremental model?",
        "a" : "Suggested by Mills 1980",
        "b" : "In between waterfall and evolutionary",
        "c" : "Increase rework in the development process",
        "d" : "Give customers opportunity to delay decisions",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 3
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT an advantage of Spiral Development Model?",
        "a" : "Delayed error elimination",
        "b" : "Puts quality objectives up front",
        "c" : "Integrates development and maintenance",
        "d" : "Provides a framework for simultaneous hardware/software development",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 1
    },

    {
        "question" : "Which of the following is NOT included in best practices for Rational Unified Process?",
        "a" : "Develop software iteratively",
        "b" : "Manage requirements",
        "c" : "Component based architecture",
        "d" : "Visually model software",
        "e" : "None of the above",
        "answer" : 5
    }
]